Hello.
Can you hear me all right?
I can hear you, how are you?
I'm doing well. Thank you, Annabelle.
Good. Thank you so much for taking the time to meet today. I'm so excited.
Yeah, where are you located on there? Where are you? Where are you sitting? Right now?
Right now I'm actually in Copenhagen. So I'm a little bit further than normal. Yes.
Oh my God. See, I'm up here on the beach.
Actually, I'm not.
I love it. I love it.
I want to be on the beach right now, but I'm here in my office, unfortunately.
Ah, okay.
If you're old to be able to join us at few moments.
Okay, perfect. That sounds good.
I love the way you did the website.
I like the concept. It was bright. It was precise.
And you did a good job not knowing any part we're doing. Just for looking on the website.
I mean, it was an awesome job.
Thank you. I appreciate that. I've had a lot of fun with it.
It was a great opportunity for me to do something a little bit new.
So thank you for giving me that opportunity.
So actually I've been a kite surfing in Spain.
And then I just came up to Copenhagen for a couple of days just to check it out.
Oh, so we used Spain ordinarily all the time, huh?
What do you mean Spain? I was kite surfing.
I surfing. Yes.
How about that? Now, where do you live?
I am from Colorado. Oh, so you're over there having fun then?
I am. Yes. I just had to.
I just graduated from the University of Michigan.
So I'm taking my little break.
Oh, yeah. I'm with Macy and all the gills there.
Exactly. Yeah.
All the sweat family. Yeah.
Oh, yes. That's awesome.
What was your major there?
I'm data analytics.
So I was coding.
Wow.
You did kite surfing in Spain, huh?
Yes, I did. It was.
It was a great, it was a great opportunity.
I bet it was. It was fun to do too, wasn't it?
Yes. Yes.
It was awesome.
Hi, Julie. How are you?
Well, I'm great. How are you?
I'm great. Thank you.
You back from Spain or are you still there?
I'm in Copenhagen now.
I'm just kind of jumping around for a little bit.
Wow. Well, thank you for making time for us.
I so appreciate it.
I know this is probably not at the top of your priority,
but we really appreciate all that you've done.
It is at the top of my priority.
I'm so excited to be meeting with you all.
Good. Okay.
Well, we love your website.
We've got, I've got Donna and Jennifer here.
I will show you them.
Hang on. I know.
I don't know why those that it didn't go through for the zoom
invite, but they are.
Hello.
Do you want me to try to put her on here so y'all can see her?
Okay.
But then I can't pull up.
So there were a few things that we had talked about that Dr.
Feisty had, I think, wanted.
Well, Dr. Feisty, do you want to walk through what you were talking
about? And then Addie and I had kind of gone over and sort of you
used what you said and tried to rework them a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, I'm trying to miss you where I find it.
Where I had it all listed.
Hey, let's see here.
Hang on.
And if it's okay, I'm recording this meeting just if that's,
if that's all right.
Okay.
Sure.
Thank you.
Well, let me find what I have here.
One thing in the first part, and I tried to print on this up so I
could have the website up at the same time.
But I can't.
I mean, let me actually let me just try to do that real quick.
Let's type them up.
Yeah, you can sit over here.
Okay.
All right.
So, you know, on the first page, your journey to optimal
vitality.
I mean, I guess, are you Annabelle?
First, let's talk.
Do you want to like kind of go through this with us hourly?
I know we kind of paid you the initial, but if you want to help us,
just make some changes.
We'd like to make it like over the next week, if that's possible.
100%.
Yes.
That sounds great.
Okay.
And then one of our patients was talking about EOS.
Do you know anything about that?
Like the, it's like, you know, it's like privacy.
And I, you know, I, I guess we just need to make sure that.
From a privacy standpoint.
Yeah.
Let's hit the compliant.
But if you connect it, you know, I guess that's just something to
consider and look into if we connect to the point.
So,
I had a couple questions about that as well, but we can talk about that
later just with the patient portal and connecting everything like that.
I just want to make sure that I understand everything that you guys use
before I connect, like the back end and everything like that.
But we can go over that after if you'd like.
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
So I, at the, you know, you had put integrative regenerative and
prevented medicine built on 50 years of clinical foundation and the long
view of whole body health from the inside out.
And I was,
I had kind of looked at a couple of different things.
And you guys tell me what, if you like these or not, I do like that.
But these are a couple of different options.
True health begins beneath the surface.
We practice integrative regenerative and prevented medicine and
drawing on half a century of clinical wisdom to help you heal,
strengthen and thrive from the inside out.
It's cute.
I like that.
I mean, these are all flawed, but they are just kind of like, you know,
putting in kind of a little more of what, and the other option was,
you're more than a symptom.
Our integrative regenerative and preventive approach draws on 50 years of
clinical care to support your whole health, body, mind and long-term
vitality.
Do you, do you guys like any of those, Dr. Festi?
Or do you like that?
I like that.
Okay.
But first one of the second one.
I like the second one.
It's drawing my eye more.
Is it?
Yeah.
These two.
We're more than a symptom.
I tried to print them out so you guys could all see them.
We're, and about, we're so busy.
We just, it's like, it's better than so.
I can't even imagine.
No, I can't imagine.
Don't, don't worry.
Anyway, those are a couple of things that we might change.
Yeah.
She had body and long-term vitality.
I like that.
Yeah.
It's like a one more.
Okay.
Yeah.
You can what?
I can share my screen.
So I think it's a part.
Yeah.
Right there.
Perfect.
Here.
Let's do this.
So integrative regenerative and preventive medicine builds on 50 years of clinical foundation in the long view.
Okay.
That versus.
The whole body of health.
I thought I was sure about the whole body health.
Yeah.
You know, I'm inside out.
I mean, that's okay, but I've been thinking about, well, if we change.
I thought sure what we suggested to change, but let me be something to think about.
Okay.
I kind of like true health begins beneath the surface.
We practice integrative regenerative.
I like that too.
Yeah.
That's good.
Clinical wisdom to help you heal, strengthen and thrive or help.
I don't know.
We can work on that, but that's something that we're going to have to change in.
Annabelle, if you, I need to understand how to make some changes.
You gave me access, but I'm able to like fully edit it or how that.
Okay.
So I would just go in like you're going in.
If we want to tweak it, I can go in and do that.
100%.
Yes.
What are you doing the website on?
It's on.
It's called Webflow.
So yeah, it's the easiest for the, for you to be able to manage without having to deal with the code or anything like that.
And then Rob and I had a call last week as well.
And he mentioned you all being able, like wanting to do promotions or things like that on the website or like just being able to edit a little bit more easily.
So you would, it would also allow you to do that there as well.
And pretty easily and I can, I can make like a zoom tutorial.
And so that you can watch it whenever you want to add a promotion or anything like that.
That'd be great.
Okay.
All right.
Now on the services part.
Dr. Festi, you had, do you have yours up on services?
Trying to find it here.
Do you really hang on?
I got so much going on in my laptop.
I can't even find everything.
Let me hang on up.
Let me see if I can find it.
Hang on.
Nope.
That's not it.
Oh, let's see here.
So I'm services Annabelle.
What did you have?
Can you go to services?
Yep.
Intro.
Can you see my screen still?
Yeah.
Okay.
So I'm on services.
Which part?
Okay.
So we wanted five pillars because he wanted to add some of the DNA testing to that.
Yeah.
The thing about is that there's a lot of things we do in peptides, hormones, weight loss and
wellness.
There's a slew of testing we do for all sorts of problems.
I was wondering whether that might be an area that we'd add in as far as the fifth section's
answering.
Okay.
Section of five.
Yeah.
I think.
Okay.
So I think advanced diagnostics and early detection might be a fifth.
Fifth.
A fifth one.
Yes.
Yeah.
And you could put in a DNA testing gallery, multi a cancer early detection.
Next gen.
Of course, the gen testing.
Yeah.
And then I'll go stand like an age.
I mean, all these things we do for different testing would be nice to have as a fifth pillar.
Okay.
So we'll, and I'll send you a list of all of those so that you can easily add that.
So you'll kind of understand what they are and everything.
Yeah.
And then, um, let's see.
And the services intro.
Where's the services intro on the site right here.
So this would be that paragraph.
Peptide therapist therapy, Harmon optimization, medical weight loss and wellness.
And our definition prescribed against the fifth one we just talked about.
Yes.
Fifth one.
Well, um.
So then I would add one to this as well.
Do you want to change the wording or the intro as a whole?
I just didn't like, um, and I knew it's like it.
It is.
It's a good way to say it, but I'm not sure that all of our patients are going to
understand like prescribed against your physiology.
And so I just thought maybe changing that wording a tiny bit and, you know,
even, I mean, it's, it makes a lot of sense, but it just kind of, I don't know.
100%. Yep, for sure.
So five pillars changing that wording a tiny bit.
What about you guys?
Do you see anything?
So where is it?
Show the five pillars.
Well, she's going to add it here.
I'll add the fifth one over here.
Yeah.
Can you show the four?
Can you show?
Can you scroll down for the four pillars?
Okay.
I don't need it is.
I know.
Harmon.
My great loss.
And then the fifth one would be down here right now.
What is going on?
Um, like the advanced testing.
Do you like that?
We don't have to do pillars.
You can, this is all this.
Did you not get the website?
I'd send it to you.
We were supposed to take notes for this.
These are just the notes that we, that Dr. Festi had come up with.
And we kind of adding, I kind of changed it a little bit.
What do you think?
I have to go through it all.
Okay.
So this is what it is.
This, if you can look at here.
Um,
Also at the beginning in a bill, it's a 60 minute.
Um, a 60 minute, a consultation, not 90.
Okay.
So this would be fine.
This is how it looks.
Okay.
There's the fourth.
Yeah.
And then she would just add advanced testing here.
And then I also wanted to clarify the complimentary consultation.
Sorry, what?
The complimentary consultation is something you still provide.
Yes.
Okay.
Great.
But just not 90 minutes.
Perfect.
Uh, okay.
A practice built on legacy, a future built on you.
I love that.
That's so good.
Uh, if I don't help, can she use to operate the strong clinical foundations
established by our founder, Dr. Joseph Festi, while he is no longer seeing
patients and is now an administrative and advisory role.
He remains a guiding source of research inside an educational
leadership as we carry forward his 50 years of expertise.
I love that.
Do you like that, Dr. Festi?
Yes, I do.
That's fine.
Sure.
Okay.
And I love this care here reads more like a relationship than an appointment
measurement.
That's right here with my picture.
Uh, I had mentioned that there's a, uh, there's a link we could do to my CV,
which is, uh, 55 pages that people like to look at.
And then you can see what's happened in the past.
So you just put a little link there says link to whatever the CV.
Something like that.
Yeah.
So 56 years of all of this.
Um, what, there's one place in here that says that this clinic is 56 years old.
This clinic is not his, his, um, his.
Right.
It's no BGIN and fertility, but so the, so the experience is 50,
over 50 years of experience, but not the clinic itself. Okay.
And then we can send you his CV.
So you could just add a link to that. Okay.
And then I'll be tweak mine a little bit and give you a.
And carry my tweak hers.
Okay. And then as far as your headshots, do you have ones that would fit?
Yeah. Um, where are those? Do we have, I can send those to her. Okay.
Yeah.
You're good. Thank all of her. Good.
Julie. They're all a buff, all three of you. All three women were good headshots.
Yeah.
I think we're happy with them. Although mine's AI and my girls are like,
it's so obviously AI, but nobody are.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, um, yeah.
So I were fine with it. Um, all right.
Start with the complimenting consultation. And this says 30 minutes.
So you need to make 60 minutes on that one.
Is this, okay. Perfect. Yeah. Right there.
So all the consultations are 60 minutes.
Right.
That's not every page. So I'll need to change that. All right. That sounds good.
Okay.
And then services menus. So we're going to change that to five pillars.
Do you like that? The five pillars? I think it looks cool.
It's cool.
Um, we need to add all of our peptides. I think, um, and so I.
Yeah. All the peptides. Exactly.
Do you send a list of all of the peptides and maybe add something where and say that we all,
we have more because there's so many that we have keeping up with all of them.
But we also have to make sure we're not marketing it. We have to say it the right way.
And I think you did say it the right way, Annabelle, or it's not like you can't really advertise peptides because some of them are not FDA approved.
So you have to, uh, prescribed.
So let's see. I think I like how you can read all of them on one little.
I know I do too. It's really well.
Uh, I had put on the peptide intro peptide therapy works best when it's personal at vital health.
Every treatment is guided by your labs and hang on.
I just went away.
Well.
Your labs and goals recommended only when your full clinical picture supports it.
Do you like that to be right here in the description?
We have a method that stimulates cellular regrow systems targeted.
I think, um, I think that.
We have to do something like that because we can't advertise that it stimulates cellular regrow.
You know what I mean?
It's just legally like a regulatory standpoint. You're not really supposed to say it does this.
You can say in these worlds, it's thought to do the, you know, so.
Okay.
Some words. Yeah. Um.
And then, um, are we going to faster? Is it okay?
Okay.
Uh, on the hormones section.
Yep.
Can you go there?
Yeah.
Under the French is under the, uh, under the women.
Is that, uh, as much as, uh, almost 90% 100% are without testosterone.
Admit a pause.
And so it could vary 50% between days of 2050.
But after a minute pause, 100% lack of testosterone.
Yeah.
Yeah, we could put that in there.
I had said, let's say you, okay.
So on hormone optimization, bioidentical hormone therapy for men and women,
the long view of hormone picture tested quarterly and adjusted at micro dose precision.
I do like that.
Yeah.
Uh, Dr. Fessy had kind of wanted some of the symptoms in there.
So not necessarily, I kind of like what you have there, but somewhere.
Maybe something hormones touch nearly everything.
If you're struggling with sleep, weight, energy, libido, migraines,
depression, hot flashes, night sweats or difficult periods,
your hormones are likely involved.
Yeah.
I think something like that, Julie, attitude for women and for men.
It's not going to be, you know, probably involving, uh, basically fatigue,
uh, libido issues, uh, probably involving high cholesterol, high LDL.
I mean, I could listen to other things for men too, as far as symptoms of concern.
Yeah.
Okay.
You have that under what we treat.
She does have a lot of that under what we treat.
Um, well, what we treat is different than symptoms.
Oh, that's good.
Well, maybe not.
I guess it'd be okay.
It tells you like, you like this one.
Like how it says fatigue.
Yeah.
Like it's emotional to you kind of.
So Annabelle, that sentence that I just said, I'll send you,
I'll send you my little PDF and I'll circle the things that we are talking about that we like.
Okay.
Um, and then, you know, there's also.
We're seeing that.
Never seems like a vaginal dryness.
Uh, it's a very common area.
Yeah.
I know that's the symptom.
I just have it.
And then bioidentical therapy protects post-menopausal women against heart disease,
dementia, urinary incontinence, collagen loss and skin elasticity.
They may also experience fatigue, disrupted sleep, weight gain, metabolic changes,
vaginal dryness, painful intercourse, mood changes, anxiety, depression.
I mean, it's like a.
That list speaks to me because.
Yeah, because it's like people that are like, Oh, now I get it.
Yeah, but you didn't know what it was.
Right.
So I'll give you that list and see if we can incorporate, just make it,
you have a lot of it on there, but maybe not all of it.
And we'll see if we can incorporate some of that.
Third column, huh?
And a third column or 30.
Yeah.
Over here, maybe.
Okay.
And then.
Also, one thing I thought might be important, hormonal imbalances don't only affect older women,
adolescents and young adults experience PMS, thyroid issues, PCOS, which is now different,
or infertility are also candidates for careful hormonal support.
Yeah.
Do you like that?
Dr. Festi.
Okay.
I like that.
Yeah.
I can relate to it.
And then for men.
I thought somewhere we could put testosterone, DHTA, thyroid and cortisol are interdependent.
A shift in one reshapes the others.
Men's hormone optimization at vital health begins with comprehensive labs and targets lean
muscle, libido, cognitive function, cardiovascular protection, and long horizon vitality.
Yeah.
I like that better because that one shifts the rest follows a little bit differently.
I love the way you said it.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then I gave a list of everything that men with low testosterone can experience.
Right.
Okay.
So Annabelle, this might be kind of what?
Even the man that.
That's good too.
I like that.
Okay.
Under the man.
Under man.
It's like fatigue and low energy, reduced libido and sexual dysfunction, loss of lean
muscle mass, increased body fat, particularly around the abdomen, brain fog and difficulty
concentrating, mood changes, irritability and depression, poor sleep and insomnia, decreased
bone density, hair thinning, reduced motivation and drive and cardiovascular changes and decreased
stamina.
Yeah.
I like the way they're written.
Well sent, this is a lot.
Annabelle, so I'll just send you this whole PDF and circle kind of what we would love to
incorporate.
If it doesn't make sense, I don't know how difficult it is to add all this stuff to a
website.
So you have to guide us to and what you can reasonably do and what you can't.
Yeah.
This is all a very, an addable.
Okay.
Yeah.
This won't take very long.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
One thing.
I had a testimonial section down here on the homepage.
Is this something that you guys wanted to include or do you want me to remove it?
I love that.
Yes.
I love it.
We have a lot of testimonials we can put in there.
Yeah.
We can put more in there if you want to because we have over 85 or 95 star reviews because
awesome.
We can have it could be like a moving thing of all of the moving slides are almost of
all of the reviews.
If you'd like that, I'd love people love to see five star reviews that they go by that
a lot and make it a decision to come in.
So that's why I think it would be nice to have all the five star reviews.
Like you said, maybe way it could be shown with this slide through it or whatever it
may take.
But well, it should do help a lot for people coming into the clinic.
Awesome.
Let's add it.
That sounds great.
Can you add it where every time somebody adds a new review, it automatically goes on
the website?
For sure.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
That would be great.
And then the shop.
Do we have that on there?
I don't know.
I'm just going to ask about that.
Okay.
We would love to add a supplement shop.
Yeah.
We have a Shopify currently.
Sorry.
You are camera shy.
I need to see her.
Yeah.
So we do we do currently have the Shopify, but I'm not sure we don't have a lot of supplements
and we can't legally add a lot of our supplements, so I'm not sure what we can do on that.
Why can't we legally add them?
They won't allow us to add on without private labeling them.
We're like a lot of our comfort labeling.
So we are we have five or six right now, but we can't do the rest.
We can.
Can we not just sell them non private label on our I mean, it like we can less than brand.
We can't let the supplements transformation, transformation that says orthomolecular does
know it.
Quick silver does not.
We have the private label all this.
So if you're private label, it's okay if you're private label, Jennifer.
It can get pricey.
But yeah, we can do that.
Well, I mean, to me, we should probably live all of anywhere.
I think it'd be good idea that we need to get anywhere else, you know, we could probably
be one of them would be nice.
It's just nice.
Annabel because we do a lot of ours on telehealth.
And so when I'm talking to patients and I recommend, you know, vitamin D three with
K or, you know, our methyl B vitamins, like it would be easy for me to say, hey, just
go to our shop.
I'll put it in your cart, but what's happening now is they're like, Oh, I can't really come
into the office.
I'll just order on Amazon.
And we really don't want that.
Yeah.
We want them to use what we're using.
Right.
So, okay, so when you say that you want them to be able to add it to the cart, that would
have to come directly from what do you like when they order it?
What do you recommend they order it from?
That's not Amazon.
Does that make sense?
I will have it here and package it here.
And we were going to get all the big supply.
We have a huge supply room that we can package it and send it out if they order it.
But I guess we could connect to Amazon and then I don't know.
Can you?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Yeah.
We're not going to do Amazon at first.
We were just going to do Shopify.
We were going to use Shopify.
And we use our own stuff recently, order it through the company and then they order
through us.
And then it's like a third party seller, pretty much.
Okay.
So, everything is on Shopify that people would want to buy.
Then we could connect the Shopify.
Let me look into it.
But I think we could connect Shopify to Webflow.
And okay, let me think about that.
But yes.
Yeah.
How we're doing it now.
There's another stuff we're involved in it.
Okay.
I just can't think of it because it's Shopify.
But payment.
Okay.
Well, you guys work on that and then let her know.
I don't know anything about that.
Yeah.
So I think it would be ideal if we could do it, but I don't, it's not, you know, I don't
know how to make it happen.
Closer.
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
Yeah.
We use Clover.
Clover.
Yeah.
That's who ships the products to the patients.
No, we do.
That's our shop.
Well, we ship it.
Okay.
Clover is the payment system on the website.
Our website is on there.
It's a, it's a whole thing.
Okay.
If you found an easier way, please let us know.
That's just all we, we've been told.
Okay.
Got it.
Let me look into that.
There's definitely an easier way.
I just need to do a little bit of research before I speak on it.
Yeah.
Perfect.
But yeah, I mean, I think, do you guys have other?
So, I mean, essentially we're going to change a little bit of the wording.
We're going to add a fifth peril.
A pillar.
We're going to kind of create the symptoms for men and women that they might be going through.
We're going to add advanced diagnostics and early detection pillar with DNA testing.
We're going to add the gallery, multi-cancer early detection, glycanage, next gen, cognitive
you, and more.
And then try to work on the shop.
But does anybody else have it?
Like, does that, is there anything else that you, when looking at the website that you were
worried about or wanted to.
So are I.
Go back to the first page of him.
If you could.
Very first page.
Where's my butterfly going to be?
It's a.
It's a little bit of flying the upper corner, one up there in the upper left-hand side,
though, but we don't make one that's alive.
That.
That flutters if you could.
We have one on our website is a, it's a colored one on the very end of our website.
There are two of them.
There's a one that first apart in the one, the last part, little bitty, little bitty one that
you could be floating up there in the corner if you wanted to.
Alive.
Got one.
You've got one.
We could try to make it.
I actually saw a hummingbird outside the window today that you would love.
I think it's like Dr. Bessie would love looking at it right over there.
Stay up and up there.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I love it.
Are we going to put our love on the website?
Yeah.
It's assisting to be bigger.
I think maybe the vital health and the, the hummingbird should be bigger.
I think so.
Exactly right.
Yeah.
So for older eyes, you can't be like you guys can't.
I can do that.
That sounds good.
People forget that.
Oh, and we also need to take out since 19.
Yeah.
That's the same.
Okay.
Perfect.
Then as far as the patient portal goes, is it okay that it connects to this for now or would.
Okay.
We just have to figure out.
How are we doing it now?
Then the order form.
We need to add the order form.
Yeah.
Patients can order their, their stuff online.
What do you think it should be?
You can probably be right next to the patient portal.
You could say like order form or.
So right next to patient portal, put order or.
Order order.
Reorder form.
Something.
Reorder form or.
I don't know.
Something with a word it.
But yeah.
We have it on our current website.
Yeah.
How do we.
We have it on our current website.
It is like hormone reorder form.
It's in the left corner.
When you click.
Yeah.
Form on reorder.
Okay.
And that is.
Yeah.
And you can probably make it look a little better.
Sure.
Okay.
Cool.
And then this is the shop you're talking about.
Yes.
You know, we have about 25 or 30 subjects on there.
All private label.
I think that would be good idea.
Jennifer, how expensive is it for private label?
You can get pretty pricey.
You have to order at least 40 at one time.
And then there's also a startup fee.
So I'll get all that information.
I'll send it to you.
Yeah.
I think private label would be good for it.
So sure they think so. Yeah.
Yes.
Is patient is connecting it to servo with patient.
Is it patient.
Information.
We got to make sure that's a clean.
Oh.
So the servo is, is, is the big employees.
Yeah.
What about your website?
She's going to talk about direct EOS or what?
Would you say you're beginning?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Gary was talking about that.
It has to be EOS.
I don't know.
There's, you know.
There's something.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
Don't you think that would be for the actual like login part?
Yeah.
So when they're in that login, they're safe.
Like, yeah.
I haven't touched this.
So I think that that still is EOS like compliant.
It's encrypted.
Yeah.
So I don't think, I think that that we're safe on all of those.
I just thought maybe we should look into it just to make sure.
So we'll look into that.
I'll look into it too.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
Okay.
And then if we can add those IV services.
Oh, yeah.
No, she has.
Can you show her that IVs weren't they on there?
I thought they were.
Then there are other website or I think.
I believe on your website.
No, I think they are.
No, those are on our website.
Yes.
But if we can add them to the new one.
Oh, this one.
I be therapy.
Yeah.
Okay.
I be menu.
Yeah.
So, um.
Like we need to advertise like we have ozone and.
The nutritional IVs.
Yeah.
The IVs and ozone need to be their own, like.
They're, I mean, sorry.
Yeah.
They're a category.
Because ozone can also be rectal and vaginal.
Yeah.
Not just IV.
And excess zones.
And excess zones as well.
Yeah.
Regenerative medicine.
Would that be here?
Or would that needs to be designed on separate pillar?
Yeah.
So she, she does have it here.
It's just, it's just not as prominent.
So we need to make that a little more prominent.
Like the, um.
The vital health IV menu extends beyond X.
Yeah.
Also, Julie, when you do a little, maybe a little, a little discussion
about the value of ozone.
Whether it's the protocols, just the value.
Why we want the use for ozone is used for as well as IV.
Like IV drips would be used for.
Yeah.
We have for it in the same way we do the peptide since it, you know,
we have for it.
Like not saying that it's proven to do this, but it's, you know, in, you know,
so we'll word it the correct way.
Um, do you want the IV section to be like a sixth pillar?
Or do you just want me to emphasize it more in this section?
I think so.
Because we're trying to build that IV room.
But I kind of like it as wellness and rejuvenation on its own.
Because then it kind of almost stands out more.
And because there's so many IVs, I feel like it wouldn't get lost.
I feel like six pillars are going to get lost.
But this, when they scroll down, it's going to have another whole, you know.
Yeah.
So what, so is wellness and rejuvenation part of the pillars?
Yes.
That's the fourth pillar.
Okay.
So that would.
Oh, it is.
So it is with it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Just.
On that page.
Right.
There, they're proximally.
Nope.
No, go down, if you would.
Go down and down.
There we go.
Some more.
Some more down.
There we go.
Down a little bit more.
Where I said X is going to explain.
Uh, it's actually 7% by at birth.
But by age 30, it drops down 90%.
Uh, okay.
So 90% the exosome, the stem cells, I mean, drop down 90%.
That's why we don't use stem cells after age 30.
But we can use exosomes to, to, they die.
Okay.
Can we, can, is there like a study that we can go to when they say that?
Like where did you get that information?
Is there a study that proves that?
Like we need to be able to.
Prove it to, because it, because from a regulatory standpoint, you know,
we have to save like from this, this study or whatever, you know,
well, I mean,
the information came from a certain study.
I look it up because it's been our, in my slides for almost five years
about the fact that it's 30.
It drops down 90% the stem cells now, not the exosomes.
Yeah.
Just look it up.
Get on there if we have a legitimate source for it.
Yeah.
And we can also put on there too.
It's a really interesting.
There's a, as a, as a, maybe a icon that says, if you want to know about
about exosome, here's a 45 page dissertation all about exosomes.
So it's, I have, I've used before.
We can, we can actually, if they want to, to, to relate to that thing,
they got to click on a detailed explanation of exosome.
They wanted to, we could do that.
That sounds like a plasma as well.
Oh, yeah.
That's a big one.
Young plasma also is a big one.
Yeah.
Right.
You want that in this section as well?
Yes.
Okay.
I think that's all I can think of.
Yeah.
We have the cognitive view. We have the carotid on there.
Did you have the carotid ultrasound on there?
That should be.
What else did we get?
We have, we had that.
That's the product.
That's the credit ultrasound.
Hey, Charlie.
HRV that we need that on there.
Oh, yeah.
Body comp.
And body comp.
Where would that be?
That would probably be part of the, well, we put that as part of our hormone program.
So maybe as part of the testing, maybe part of advanced testing.
Yeah.
Advanced testing.
It's the best place to put it.
Yeah.
Let me, where would that be on your website?
It's not on our current website.
Okay.
It's.
Yeah.
When you send me those notes, will you just include like what the description that you'd like for that part?
Yes.
Okay.
Great. Thank you.
And do you want that in the wellness and rejuvenation section as well? Or.
Do you want to be.
Yes.
Testing.
Yeah.
Okay.
So do you want that in like a separate tab up here?
No.
Doesn't it already have its own filler?
So the pillars are peptide, hormone, weight loss, wellness and rejuvenation.
And the dance says, Oh, yeah, we're making that.
Oh, right.
So it'll be diagnostics and early detection.
Correct.
Okay.
So that'll be added there.
Yeah.
Again.
And she has it on there.
She also has next gen.
Yeah.
She has all that.
I mean, I can't make sure to have this little thing.
Nutritional injections.
I don't know if we have that or gut health.
Heavy metal testing.
Oh, yeah.
And that talks PRP.
And that's not a botox and PRP aren't there during tests.
So heavy metal testing and.
I map.
The I'm a GI map. Yeah.
Yeah.
And the gene test.
The gene.
We do a six to eight gene test.
We do the gallery of tests.
We do the next gen test.
And then we're going to offer a full body MRI.
If we want to, as far as further investigation,
how much you want to put on here.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll send, I'll send you all of these notes kind of with these
additions that are like kind of a lot.
Yeah.
A lot of them.
That's right.
For a lot.
Yeah.
Like those we don't, you know, it's not like we do them all the
time, but we have the capability and we'd like to,
to make sure that patients know that, you know,
for sure.
That makes sense.
Okay.
Yeah, that sounds great.
I have the basic notes and then everything else.
What I would love it if you could send it over.
And then I can add it and send it back to you.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
And then as far as Instagram goes, do you want to have that in a
separate meeting?
Do you want to talk about that in a separate meeting or?
What are your thoughts on that?
My next patient is in 30 minutes.
So I have time.
You have time, Annabelle.
We would love to talk about it.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
And I have my, I'm going to go get Addie because she,
my little 14 year old daughter is so interested in this too.
And I showed her everything that you've had.
And she was like, Oh, that's so cool.
So I want her to listen.
But you guys start talking and I'll.
So Jennifer, do you want to, do you want to get over there with
Jennifer and y'all?
Okay.
Awesome.
Let me just pull up.
Okay.
Perfect.
So I kind of just want to get a little bit of an understanding of
what your, what everybody's goals are with the Instagram.
I think we can kind of go in a variety of different directions
with social media.
So I just kind of want to get an understanding of your thoughts
and desires.
So I sent Julie.
I'll show my screen again.
Just a second.
Um,
this, and as far as like wording and everything like that goes,
don't, you don't need to look at that, but that, that'll obviously
be changed.
Um, but this is kind of what like the general, I guess vibe would
be of the first Instagram posts that I just curated pretty
quickly.
Um, just to kind of see what your guys' thoughts were.
Um, it, this one is like a six.
Um, it's called the carousel.
This is a six carousel, like grouping of images, you know,
when you scroll through, um, and this would be like the
introduction poster.
Like, I've noticed that you don't have any Instagram posts
right now.
So I think that this would be giving a little bit more of an
introduction as to what battle health does.
Um, and I think that would be the, a good first place to begin.
Um, and then I think the Instagram, it could be helpful just to
have it as like a place where people can come and kind of
understand all of the services you all provide.
So I was kind of thinking that we could go more of that angle.
Um, and then I also wanted to hear your guys' thoughts and
feedback as well.
Well, Annabelle, I have done about four podcasts and have been
on, I have put them on Instagram and TikTok.
Awesome.
Now what I want to do is every Monday, I want to publish a
podcast on all the different subjects I can think of.
So that would be going on for months.
Now, when I tried to publish them, didn't turn out too good as
far as how to put them on Instagram and TikTok.
I could put them on Instagram, but I didn't know how to put them
on TikTok as well.
Okay.
But I do think that every Monday morning I would create a
podcast and the podcast would then be published for that day.
So for a while there, everybody was looking for the next
podcast until I stopped.
So people got to the point they were looking for the next one.
So I can keep that up on a regular basis.
The second thing I want to do is a live webinar.
Or so that I would, for instance, I would have Julie in there and
we would talk about different things.
I haven't invited guests to come in.
Do you want those on?
I mean, I think that we should start the Instagram kind of with
the posts, like just regular posts and then have your web,
like your, you know, after a couple of the main ones that, I
mean, a couple of the first ones, like one, two, three, and then
a live one from you.
And then, you know, every Monday we can start doing it.
But I think that when we need to start our Instagram, I think
we need to have like some of our, like exactly what we do.
And what she's talking about, just kind of explaining who we are,
what we do.
And then, and I think that you can very well beyond even the first
one, kind of talking about it, but more of a general information
of what vital health is all about versus, you know, your
specific ones are super interesting.
And I love those.
And I think those would be greater a little bit further down the
line just in a few weeks.
But right.
For the first ones, I think just a big picture of what we do is
better.
Okay.
Great.
So I think the first one, this was kind of meant to be like one
post and that people would slide through.
It's called a carousel.
And so I was thinking that for the first post, you would have like
a little bit of an introduction, what vital health does, just kind
of the idea, the general gist of the idea and the values behind
vital health.
And then the next couple would maybe be about, you know, what
vital health and then the next couple would maybe be about the
different services that you all offer.
And just so that when people searching on Instagram, they're
able to get a general feel for what your business is about and
what services you can offer them.
And then maybe after we describe all the services you all offer,
then you could begin your Monday posts or throughout posting all
of the services that you all offer.
We could include the Monday posts or the podcast or the webinars,
things like that.
Does that sound okay?
Sure does.
Absolutely.
Okay.
And do you all know how frequently you would want to be posting on
Instagram, ideally?
Every day.
I was kidding.
As much as possible.
Okay.
I think the most, the more we do, the better I would think anyway to
do it.
Okay.
We only have like 200 patients on there.
Not even patients.
They're just random people.
But one thing I think, you know, I am about asked if we had
pictures that we wanted to use.
And I said, not at this point, but I know that we've talked about,
I love the ones that you picked because they're the least
stocky looking, but they still are, they're still, you know,
they're not our clinic, obviously.
So I don't know if you guys, if we want to get a photographer and
kind of take pictures of people in our clinic and then have
her use those before she starts, you know, is to kind of welcome
everybody to the new office.
This is our office and have more of our stuff in there.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It's a good idea.
Or do you want to just start with like this?
These are great.
They're beautiful.
They are beautiful.
Also, I think a thing on social media right now is I'm not sure
how you guys feel, but it's not like the, you don't need to
have a photographer come and take pictures if you didn't want to.
Like it would also be cool if you just took like a video and just
did like a little introduction of like what the office looked like,
or just take a couple of pictures of your on your own phone.
I don't want you to feel pressure to like get a photographer because
I think people would still love to just see what it's like from your
perspective.
Just like this is when you walk into the office, just random videos
showing off the new, the space in general, I think could also be very
valuable.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
I think if I make some of those and send them to you, that sounds
great.
Did you get to play with?
Yeah.
That sounds awesome.
And then as far so everyday posting, um, am I, do you want me to
send those to somebody?
And then they post to them themselves?
And maybe, how about I just, I can do it.
Or once a week.
I don't, I don't think every, I think that like.
At least twice a week.
Yeah.
Okay.
Two to three times a week.
And then they would send them to, she would send them to Jennifer.
Okay.
Or you want to be in charge of it or.
Or Scott.
And.
We'll figure that out.
We'll figure it out.
Yeah.
So how about I just generate a couple like this.
Uh, and I can send them to you all and you can post them.
And if it works, and we can continue doing it.
And then at some point, um, we can find a way to automate them.
And so that they can be created for you.
And we can just kind of work through the process and see how it goes.
But I'll work on generating a few more carousels like this and see how that
process works.
Does that sound okay?
Yeah, that's perfect.
Okay.
Perfect.
And do you have examples of other websites that you've worked on?
Yeah.
I can send you, um, I can send you a couple.
I have been working for a life coach and then, um, uh, private aviation company.
And then as well as like a run club company as well.
Um, so I can send you a few of their websites.
Um, if that'd be helpful.
Thank you.
Of course.
I haven't reconstructed a website completely like I reconstructed your yours.
Um, so I, but I have, um, like gone through and changed websites based off of what the clients want.
Um, so it's not like a full rebrand and it's not as drastic of a change, but I can definitely show you some things I've been working on.
Thank you.
This is also cool that you're doing this.
We love it, Annabelle.
Like I told them you just do it and you're just like, it's kind of amazing what you're doing.
So impressive.
Thank you.
Well, I'm very grateful for you all.
It's, it's a really, it's a, it's a great learning opportunity for me as well.
So I'm grateful that you're, that you're trusting me and I'm so excited to be working with you all.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, next steps, I guess we need to send you the PDF and we will, and we'll just kind of get together and write down everything that we sort of remember that we talked about and you have it recorded.
So if we forget something, you'll have it on there.
And then, yeah, and then send us a couple of those Instagram posts and we'll go from there.
That sounds great.
That sounds awesome.
Um, well, perfect.
And then if there's anything else you all think about, um, feel free to just let me know and we'll be in touch.
Okay.
All right.
That sounds great.
Thank you guys.
Have a great rest of your day.
All right.
You too.
Bye bye.